<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Arabic (Saudi Arabia) / العربية (السعودية) generated by BuildAutoStrings -->
<resources>
	<!-- No entry for menu.sequential.download -->
	<string name="rcm_ftux_heading">مرحبا بكم في عرض اكتشافات السرب</string>
	<string name="rcm_ftux_info">تعرض طريقة العرض هذه محتوى مرتبطا بطريقة ما بالمحتوى الذي تقوم بتنزيله بالفعل.
يمكنك الاطلاع على مزيد من المعلومات حول هذه الميزة في صفحة &lt;;A HREF=\";https://wiki.biglybt.com/w/Swarm_Discoveries\";>;Swarm Discoveries Wiki Page&lt;;/A>;.\n
\n
\n
\n
افتراضيا هذه الميزة لا تسمح للمواقع تعقب داخل ملفات تورنت لاستخدامها لاكتشاف الملفات تورنت ذات الصلة.
يمكنك تفعيل واحدة من مجموعتين من مواقع تعقب تورنت.
اعتمادا على الاختيار الذي تقوم به تحت نتائج اكتشاف السرب قد تتضمن ملفات تورنت التي تحتوي على قائمة محدودة مسبقا مختارة من مواقع التعقب، القائمة التي تستند على حسن نية الاعتقاد المعقول أن مواقع التعقب تلك تتبع فقط استضافة المحتوى الذي هو قانوني و لا تنتهك حقوق أي طرف ثالث، بما في ذلك حقوق الطبع والنشر، ولكنك تفترض، ونحن نخلي، جميع المخاطر بما في ذلك استخدام مواقع التعقب تلك.
إذا كنت ترغب في تفعيل مواقع التعقب هذه بعد قراءة &lt;;A HREF=\";https://wiki.biglybt.com/w/Swarm_Discoveries\";>;هنا&lt;;/A>; حول تلك المواقع وبعض المخاطر في استخدامها، حدد الخيار أدناه.</string>
	<string name="rcm_ftux_option_preselect">تمكين BiglyBT مواقع التتبع المحددة مسبقا.
لقد قرأت &lt;;A HREF=\";https://wiki.biglybt.com/w/Swarm_Discoveries\";>;هنا&lt;;/A>; و \n
\n
&lt;;A HREF=\";http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/BitTorrent#Legal_issues\";>;هنا&lt;;/A>; حول تلك المواقع وبعض مخاطر استخدامها، وأنا أفهم وأوافق على أن BiglyBT لا تتحمل أية مسؤولية من أي نوع عن طريق تفعيل هذه الوظيفة واستخدام أي من المتتبعين.
أوافق على أن مسؤوليتي هي ضمان تحميل المحتوى القانوني وغير المخالف فقط.</string>
	<string name="rcm_ftux_info2">If you would like Swarm Discoveries to find files \"related to\" your existing torrent files from all sources, not just the BiglyBT Pre-Selected tracker sites, select the option below.</string>
	<string name="rcm_ftux_option_all">ENABLE ALL discoveries related to my existing torrent files, irrespective of what tracker sites the torrent contains.
I have read &lt;A HREF=\"https://wiki.biglybt.com/w/Swarm_Discoveries\">here&lt;/A> and   &lt;A HREF=\"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/BitTorrent#Legal_issues\">here&lt;/A> about those sites and some risks of using them,   and I UNDERSTAND AND AGREE that BiglyBT has no responsibility whatsoever with my enabling this function and using all discoveries.
I agree that it is my responsibility to ensure that I am only downloading lawful and non-infringing content.</string>
	<string name="rcm_ftux_smallprint">Any use of BiglyBT that violates the rights of any person or entity is not allowed.
&lt;A HREF=\"https://wiki.biglybt.com/w/FAQ_Legal\">More&lt;/A>.</string>
	<!-- No entry for rcm.ftux2.heading -->
	<string name="rcm_ftux2_info">For tracker sites not included in the tracker sites pre-selected by BiglyBT,   we additionally warn that some of those tracker sites might be accused of being more likely to track torrent   files that might infringe upon the rights of others, including copyright, and might include more \"adult\" content,   some of which might be alleged to infringe upon the rights of others.\n
\n
Given how Swarm Discoveries works,   third party torrent files that might automatically be considered \"related\" to the torrent files on your device   which are found by the way of either BiglyBT pre-selected tracker sites or \"all\" discoveries, might be \"related\" only by virtue   of the fact that if you and other users have \"ABC.torrent,\" for example, and many or some of those other users have   \"XXX.torrent,\" Swarm Discoveries might consider the \"XXX.torrent\" to be \"related\".
You might want to take additional care in selecting what Swarm Discovery content you wish to download,   as well as then make available for uploading.</string>
	<string name="rcm_ftux2_agree">I understand and agree.
Enable all discoveries related to my existing torrent files, irrespective of what tracker sites the torrent contains.
I have read &lt;A HREF=\"https://wiki.biglybt.com/w/Swarm_Discoveries\">here&lt;/A> and   &lt;A HREF=\"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/BitTorrent#Legal_issues\">here&lt;/A> about those tracker sites and some risks of using them,   and I UNDERSTAND AND AGREE that BiglyBT has no responsibility whatsoever with my enabling this function.
I agree that is my responsibility to ensure that I am only downloading lawful and non-infringing content.</string>
	<string name="drawer_rcm">اكتشافات السرب</string>
</resources>
