<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Occitan / Occitan generated by BuildAutoStrings -->
<resources>
	<!-- No entry for menu.sequential.download -->
	<!-- No entry for rcm.ftux.heading -->
	<string name="rcm_ftux_info">This view displays content that is related in some way to the content that you are already downloading.
You can read more about this feature on our &lt;A HREF=\"https://wiki.biglybt.com/w/Swarm_Discoveries\">Swarm Discoveries Wiki Page&lt;/A>.
\n
\n
By default this feature does not allow tracker sites within your torrent files to be used to discover related torrent files.
You may enable one of two sets of bittorrent tracker sites.
Depending on the choice you make below the Swarm Discovery results may include torrent files that contain a limited pre-selected list of tracker sites,   which list is based upon our good faith reasonable belief that those tracker sites only track or host content that is lawful and does not infringe upon the rights, including copyright, of any third party,   but you assume, and we disclaim, all risk including of using those tracker sites.
If you would like to enable those tracker sites after you read &lt;A HREF=\"https://wiki.biglybt.com/w/Swarm_Discoveries\">here&lt;/A> about those sites and some risks of using them, select the option below.</string>
	<string name="rcm_ftux_option_preselect">ENABLE BiglyBT Pre-Selected Tracker Sites.
I have read &lt;A HREF=\"https://wiki.biglybt.com/w/Swarm_Discoveries\">here&lt;/A> and   &lt;A HREF=\"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/BitTorrent#Legal_issues\">here&lt;/A> about those sites and some risks of using them,   and I UNDERSTAND AND AGREE that BiglyBT has no responsibility whatsoever with my enabling this function and using any of those trackers.
I agree that it is my responsibility to ensure that I am only downloading lawful and non-infringing content.</string>
	<string name="rcm_ftux_info2">If you would like Swarm Discoveries to find files \"related to\" your existing torrent files from all sources, not just the BiglyBT Pre-Selected tracker sites, select the option below.</string>
	<string name="rcm_ftux_option_all">ENABLE ALL discoveries related to my existing torrent files, irrespective of what tracker sites the torrent contains.
I have read &lt;A HREF=\"https://wiki.biglybt.com/w/Swarm_Discoveries\">here&lt;/A> and   &lt;A HREF=\"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/BitTorrent#Legal_issues\">here&lt;/A> about those sites and some risks of using them,   and I UNDERSTAND AND AGREE that BiglyBT has no responsibility whatsoever with my enabling this function and using all discoveries.
I agree that it is my responsibility to ensure that I am only downloading lawful and non-infringing content.</string>
	<string name="rcm_ftux_smallprint">Any use of BiglyBT that violates the rights of any person or entity is not allowed.
&lt;A HREF=\"https://wiki.biglybt.com/w/FAQ_Legal\">More&lt;/A>.</string>
	<!-- No entry for rcm.ftux2.heading -->
	<string name="rcm_ftux2_info">For tracker sites not included in the tracker sites pre-selected by BiglyBT,   we additionally warn that some of those tracker sites might be accused of being more likely to track torrent   files that might infringe upon the rights of others, including copyright, and might include more \"adult\" content,   some of which might be alleged to infringe upon the rights of others.\n
\n
Given how Swarm Discoveries works,   third party torrent files that might automatically be considered \"related\" to the torrent files on your device   which are found by the way of either BiglyBT pre-selected tracker sites or \"all\" discoveries, might be \"related\" only by virtue   of the fact that if you and other users have \"ABC.torrent,\" for example, and many or some of those other users have   \"XXX.torrent,\" Swarm Discoveries might consider the \"XXX.torrent\" to be \"related\".
You might want to take additional care in selecting what Swarm Discovery content you wish to download,   as well as then make available for uploading.</string>
	<string name="rcm_ftux2_agree">I understand and agree.
Enable all discoveries related to my existing torrent files, irrespective of what tracker sites the torrent contains.
I have read &lt;A HREF=\"https://wiki.biglybt.com/w/Swarm_Discoveries\">here&lt;/A> and   &lt;A HREF=\"https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/BitTorrent#Legal_issues\">here&lt;/A> about those tracker sites and some risks of using them,   and I UNDERSTAND AND AGREE that BiglyBT has no responsibility whatsoever with my enabling this function.
I agree that is my responsibility to ensure that I am only downloading lawful and non-infringing content.</string>
	<!-- No entry for rcm.view.heading -->
</resources>
